Ichikawa, can you be our student rep and read a farewell address to our graduating class?
Yeah, I don't think so.
What? No way, that's awesome!
Yeah, maybe, but this is something important that an honor student should probably do.
Someone like Ishimura or even Hara.
What about me?
Be my guest.
A farewell speech? Why not you? You've got good grades.
Got the second highest grade on our final.
Wait, that's amazing! You did?
Oh, you didn't hear. I was all happy about doing a little better and then...
Well, I got the second best grade.
You should do it!
Him? Giving a farewell speech?
Hilarious!
This isn't all about grades though.
Okay, okay. I'm not trying to force you here or anything.
But we have a rehearsal tomorrow and no one has taken the role yet.
Oh, you were all right now.
Uh...
Hmm.
Oh!
Uh!
Just until you find someone then!
If it's just rehearsal...
Then I guess I can do it.
Thank you.
Next, a farewell address from our student representative, Kiyotaro Ichikawa.
Huh?
I should have said no.
Farewell graduating students, the day your journey begins has come, despite the harsh
cold, the rays of spring fall warm upon us now, I will show up with you celebrating your
Can't hear a word.
He's just whispering.
Who is that?
He's a nervous wreck.
It sounded to me like you were whispering up there.
That's too bad, trouble with the sound system, I guess.
I died out there.
Nice try.
Whatever, I bet they'll look for someone else now, and find by me.
Let's practice, come on.
Huh?
What?
Come on, I'm not gonna do this.
I take voice lessons and stuff, don't worry.
Now, focus on your diaphragm.
Um, the diaphragm is higher up.
In closing, I hope that you all remain in good health, and accomplish great things.
And from all of us, farewell.
Wow!
That was much better!
Good job!
Standing straight like this is exhausting.
That was great!
Must be because you're second in our grade.
You're the one who gave me voice lessons just now.
Yeah, I know, but...
Why didn't you tell me?
If I was second in our grade, I'd be bragging to everyone.
It's not really that big of a deal.
School grades are nothing more than small steps.
What's important is where you let them lead you.
That's so professional!
So, the other day, you came and saw me at work, yeah?
And cuz of that, you got to see me trying my best.
I wanna see you try.
Psst!
Go out with me, please.
Sorry, I can't.
It's just... there's someone else I really like.
Yamada?
Mm-hmm.
You're better off dating someone else.
Then why do we always go out so much?
I don't wanna see the look on her face.
This guy really meant it.
I'll do it.
Huh?
The address.
It's time to stand proud.
To let her see.
To let him see.
Or so I said.
On behalf of all of us here, I wish you all the best.
Mm... quit staring.
But you asked me to sit here and watch you read your speech.
You said it was the only way it counted as practice.
Uh, sorry.
When did I start getting scared of being in front of people?
The award for best traffic safety poster goes to Kyo-Taro Ichikawa.
Congratulations.
Huh, these ignoramuses, they're nothing compared to me.
I've fallen a long way from my old self.
All right, bro.
I brought the humidifier.
And the third stuff you rub on.
Ah!
Okay, rub this on your chest.
What are you doing?
This stuff is for colds.
Whatever.
I just have to read the basic script.
It's no big deal.
What I need, though, is a haircut.
Will 2,000 yen do?
No.
I need more like 5,000.
Huh?
No way!
Are you making your haircut debut?
Great system for antisocial folks.
Okay, then.
What are you writing?
A flow chart for my conversation with the hairstylist.
I need to think up easy ways to tell them what kind of haircut I want, too.
Uh, want me to go with you?
Definitely not.
And so, I readied myself for the hair salon.
But they must have labeled me the non-social type, because we didn't share a word the whole
time.
Take a look.
Thanks.
These fancy places are something else.
And so, I'm Kiyotaro Ichikawa, and I speak for all of us.
Huh?
Quit crying!
Why should I?
And just like that, graduation was here.
Huh?
Why does this look different after just one day?
Wow!
Your hair's real short!
You look rich!
What happened?
Uh, nothing.
Just went to a new place, and it came out weird is all.
Make it sound like it wasn't the first time you ever went.
You use any wax?
Hm?
What wax?
Wait.
Hang on a second.
Hey!
Adachi!
Huh?
You got waxed on you, yeah?
Give it here.
You robbing the poor guy?
Uh, uh, uh...
I think that should do it.
Serena wants to be a hair stylist one day.
What?
I never said that.
It's just one option to look at.
Geez.
You do have really nice hair, though.
Might be able to...
There!
How's that?
Hm?
It's like he's a thug!
No one will give you crap now.
Yamada?
Don't worry.
I am a model, after all.
Just six months ago, I never could have imagined this situation.
Enough of that.
It's ribbon time.
Oh, I forgot.
But, uh...
Hm?
What's your deal, Bayashiko?
Hm...
Nothing.
Just thinking how it's all over already.
Huh?
We'll be changing classes once we start year three.
Hm.
Yeah.
They say they split up groups of troublemakers.
So you think we're troublemakers?
Well, we walk a fine line.
We might end up in separate classes.
We'll be fine.
You know that?
Not exactly.
I don't...
But...
It doesn't hurt to believe it anyway.
We're getting started!
Line up in the hall.
Uh...
Wait a sec!
You look the same as always!
Thank you, Yoshida.
Huh?
Nah, no worries.
Let's get going.
Such a pain in the butt.
Those chairs are too.
Now then.
Just gotta make sure I have my script.
Huh?
No!
What?!
You forgot your farewell speech?!
But...
Isn't it about to start?
Relax, don't worry.
I've gotcha!
I'll find it and get it over to you as fast as I can!
It's somewhere on your desk?
Wait!
I'm not gonna find any pervy stuff, am I?
Just hurry!
What do I do?
Do I tell the teachers I can't do it?
Just stop after the opening bit I do remember?
Or should I...
What's going on?
Oh, uh...
Actually...
I'll do it!
The address!
It's nothing.
Ichikawa?
Please...
Don't tell me I can do this!
Don't say it!
You can do this!
Ta-da!
That's...
It's mine.
But you hang on to it.
Now let's go!
Come on, I gotta make it!
Hurry up!
Come on!
Hold on.
Was his school this way or that way?
Okay, what's the matter?
Oh!
Hey there, newbie!
Do you happen to know the way to Daijuni Junior High?
I used to go there.
Thank goodness!
Then can you show me the way there?
Fine, keep up!
Coming!
Now then, next I would like to offer a congratulatory address to all those here today.
There's no way I can do this!
A speech with no script?
At this rate...
No!
My arm!
I can't contain it!
Make it stop!
No!
This is a graduation!
I'd better head over early and ask for advice.
Hello, Ichikawa!
So, uh...
Thank you, son.
Really.
For taking this on.
Huh?
I'm really grateful.
Now head on that way.
Attaboy!
Hang on now!
There's no way!
People might be cheering me on, but I'm still no people person!
That old me is gone!
Quit fooling yourself!
Huh?
Do you think Yamada and your teachers would cheer you on if you weren't up to this?
Don't you think that the old you was the real you?
Who found that keychain?
I apologize, but this is not open to the public.
Listen here!
My brother is acting a student rep!
Pretty impressive, isn't it?
That old me is gone!
Quit fooling yourself!
Do you think Yamada and your teachers would cheer you on if you weren't up to this?
Don't you think that the old you was the real you?
You?
Who found that keychain?
I apologize, but this is not open to the public.
Listen here!
My brother is acting a student rep!
Pretty impressive, isn't it?
Sorry!
And now a farewell address by Kiyonaro-
No!
Wait, stop!
Remember, who is it that trusts in you the most?
Is it your teachers?
Your sister?
Yamada?
No!
It's me!
You've known all along!
Don't worry!
You can do this!
I can do this!
The one who likes you more than anyone else would be me!
So don't turn your eyes from me!
Turn your eyes from me!
The day of your journey has come to me!
You've known all along!
Don't worry!
You can do this!
I can do this!
The one who likes you more than anyone else would be me!
You've known all along!
The day of your journey has come as the rays of spring fall warm upon us now!
I want to wish all of you congratulations on celebrating your graduation!
We can hear him!
We have learned much from each and every one of you!
All of us came to this school not knowing what to expect, and you welcomed us with open arms!
You leave us now as irreplaceable parts of our lives, moving on into the future!
One, I imagine, that may hold some difficult and trying moments.
But still, even still, that's the last part I remember!
But you are the ones who must take these steps forward yourselves!
Accepting that simple fact is scary, unthinkable, but you can't run away from it!
Because you have already seen the light!
It is in all of your friends, your teachers, and in all you've experienced in this place of learning!
What did he have for breakfast?
But no, it will be alright!
Don't stop trying new things!
Learn to love yourselves!
Treasure all that you've come to know!
I am Kiyotaro Ichikawa, and I speak on behalf of the student body!
That was great, Ichikawa!
Those ignoramuses, they were nothing compared to me!
Ichikawa!
Figures...
Guess I'm still me in the end!
How do you feel?
Um...
I'm doing better!
You know...
Your farewell speech today!
Oh good!
There you are!
Not him!
I am!
Oh!
And our student rep is here too!
That speech of yours was a home run!
Pulled on the heartstrings!
Empty your words were never spoken!
Ah...
Yamada...
Got a sec?
Uh...
Yamada...
I'm gonna sleep for a bit.
We...
Can just talk here.
Congratulations on graduating!
Thanks!
If he pulls anything weird...
It's this!
This!
And this!
Ah!
I'm not...
The same me from back then!
So...
Are you going to keep playing soccer in high school?
Huh?
Why would you ask?
I always saw you watching them practice even after you left the club.
Figured you must like soccer.
Uh...
Happy to hear you took that much notice!
Hold it right there!
Is that what you're thinking now?
Not really.
This is all just some empty ritual.
You're right.
I was on the youth team back in elementary school.
But sticking with it doesn't mean you can go pro.
And it's more fun just playing around.
You're impressive in that way.
Heard you're in the movies nowadays.
You're way cooler than I'll ever be.
It makes me happy really.
To see you working hard.
I respect you for it.
Same as me.
No...
That's not it.
It's not?
I like you.
I would like you...
To have this button.
I know how you feel!
Hm?
No.
I mean...
How it makes you happy to see someone working hard.
How you respect them and you're afraid they'll start to hate you so you get all worried.
And that's why...
Well...
I mean...
I...
Um...
Sorry.
There's...
Someone else I like a lot!
So I'm sorry.
My hands are full.
And I can't take that.
I know how it feels to cry over someone you like.
Yamada.
She likes me.
Right.
Graduation's over now.
See ya.
Bye.
I'll message you over Spring Break.
Huh?
Bye.
Let's see.
you over spring break our little student rep friend gave me your info when I asked him
just so you're aware what no I that's not true he didn't do that don't lie to me like that
not buying it huh
why leave with an obvious lie that makes her hate you like that
why didn't you tell her you quit because you got hurt because then she would only
love me out of pure sympathy hold on you were finally alone
huh huh did they do it in those few seconds they had i know right
i know right